<resources>
    <string name="app_name">NafplioTourGuide</string>

    <string name="CultureTab">Cultural Places</string>
    <string name="FoodTab">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="HotelsTab">Accommodation</string>
    <string name="BeachTab">Beaches</string>
    <string name="arch_museum">Archaeological Museum</string>
    <string name="arch_description">It was first built in 1713, during the second reign of the Venetians and
        is accommodated in the imposing in size as well as strict in symmetry, stone-built Venetian structure.
        Syntagmatos Square, P.C:21100, Nafplio Τel.Number: 27520 27502</string>
    <string name="war_museum">War Museum</string>
    <string name="war_description">Located in the area where the first Army Cadet School were, the War Museum
        was inaugurated at the end of 1988.The Museum is a directive of the history of the Army Cadet School.
        Amalias 22, P.C 21100, Nafplio city. Tel. Number: 27520 25591 </string>
    <string name="fol_museum">Folklore Museum</string>
    <string name="fol_description">The Peloponnesian Folklore Foundation of public benefit was established back
        in 1974. Its primary aim is the research, study and conservation of the Hellenic cultural activity.
        King Alexander 1, St, Nafplio, P.C:21100 Tel. Number: 27520 28947</string>
    <string name="palamidi">Palamidi</string>
    <string name="pal_description">The fort of the Palamidi, which has been preserved in excellent condition,
        is one of the greatest achievements of Venetian fortification architecture.</string>
    <string name="bourtzi">Bourtzi</string>
    <string name="bourtzi_description">The fort on the sea, which has remained known by its Turkish name Bourtzi,
        meaning tower, has become Nafplion\'s trademark.This small island is in the middle of the city's harbour.</string>
    <string name="synd_square">Syndagma Square</string>
    <string name="synd_description">Syndagma Square, the most historic square in Nauplion, comprises the centre
        of the city.The square was once home to the residences of many of the great fighters of the Greek revolution,
        such as Nikitaras and Theodoros Kolokotronis.</string>
    <string name="Kapod_square">Kapodistria Square</string>
    <string name="kapod_description">This square takes its name from the figure who above all others is synonymous with
        the history of the city: Ioannis Kapodistrias, the first governor of the modern Greek state.</string>
    <string name="arapakos">Arapakos</string>
    <string name="arap_description">Since 1978 , our menu includes greek cuisine, fresh fish, sea food, meat grilled or roasted and pasta dishes
         Port of Nafplio : 81 Bouboulina St.
         Tel: 27520 27675  </string>
    <string name="carr_pizza">Carrera\'s Pizza</string>
    <string name="carr_description">Traditional Italian cuisine. The pizza baked in wood oven.
         Sidiras Merarhias 9 and Polizoidou, Nafplio 211 00
         Tel: 2752 024985 </string>
    <string name="fougaro">FOUGARO Café</string>
    <string name="foug_description">Asklipiou 98, Nafplio 21100
        Tel: +30 27520.47347 </string>
    <string name="gyrokomeio">Gyrokomeio</string>
    <string name="gyr_description">We are located in Nafplio, Argolida in a modern decorated and clean place offering traditional flavors from fresh ingredients and selected meats.
         11, Sidiras Merarchias and Polizoidi - Nafplio
         Tel: +30 2752023600</string>
    <string name="acronafplia">Acronafplia Pension</string>
    <string name="acr_description">This property is 3 minutes walk from the beach.
         Efthimiopoulou 14, Nafplio, 21100, Greece
         Tel: +30 27525 00042</string>
    <string name="amalia">Amalia Nafplio</string>
    <string name="ama_description">On the outskirts of historic Nafplio, this neoclassical building offers luxurious rooms.
         Argous Street, Nafplio, 21100, Greece
         Tel: +30 2752 024 400</string>
    <string name="nafsimedon">Nafsimedon Hotel</string>
    <string name="nafs_description">This property is 6 minutes walk from the beach. Set in a mid-19th-century neoclassical house right opposite Kapodistrias Square.
          9 Sidiras Merarhias Str., Nafplio, 21100, Greece
          Tel: +30 27520-25060</string>
    <string name="klymeni">Klymeni Guesthouse</string>
    <string name="klym_description">The stone-built apartments are just 1 km from Palamidi and 1.5 km from Karathonas beach, on the outskirts of Nafplion.
          Eparchiaki Odos Nafpliou-Frouriou Palamidiou, Nafplio, 21100, Greece
          Tel: +302752096194</string>
    <string name="ancient_assini">Ancient Assini Beach</string>
    <string name="anc_description">Pebbled. Rocky on its edges. Small sized beach, seabed rocky-pebbled.</string>
    <string name="arvanitia">Arvanitia Beach</string>
    <string name="arv_description">Pebbled on its center. Rocky on its edges, access through small metallic ladders. Middle sized beach, sandy and small pebbled.
          Sea bottom: Sandy.</string>
    <string name="karathona">Karathona Beach</string>
    <string name="kar_description">Sandy throughout, sea bottom sandy as well. Large scale beach, shallow waters, proper for children and families.</string>
    <string name="kondyli">Kondyli Beach</string>
    <string name="kon_description">Thin and large pebbles, sand. Quite large as a beach. Its seabed is for the most part rocky and at some points on the left it is sandy as well.
          Quite deep, with a steep incline.</string>
    <string name="plaka">Plaka Beach</string>
    <string name="pla_description">Small and large pebbled. Quite large as a beach, interchanging. Seabed mainly sandy with some big plaques.</string>
</resources>
